5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(spotlove_logo, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot.Love Logo Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. markPassed("Back Button Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_first_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Sign in to Spot.Love label text is found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Second_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Continue with your phone number label text is found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(flag_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Country Flag Icon is found......!")
5. tap(flag_icon, 10)
9. markPassed("Country slection dropdown is opened......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(search_box, 10))
1. setText(search_box, C_Name, 10)
5. markPassed("Country Name Entered in the Search Box......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(First_index, 10))
1. tap(First_index, 10)
5. markPassed("Country Selection Successfully......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Enter_Phonenumber, 10))
1. setText(Enter_Phonenumber, PhoneNumber, 10)
5. markPassed("Phon number Entered......!")
9. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())