1. startExistingApplication("com.spotlove.releaseproduction", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Logo_Spotlove, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot.Love Logo Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_txt_first, 10))
1. markPassed("Welcome to Spot.Love lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_txt_Sec, 10))
1. markPassed("Please follow these house rules lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(first_heart_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("First Heart Icon Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Be_kind_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Be Kind lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Treat_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Treat everyone with respect and kindness lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Second_heart_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Second Heart Icon Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Be_your_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Be yourself lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Be_honest_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Be honest about your age, photos, and bio lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Third_heart_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Third Heart Icon Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Be_out_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Be outspoken lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Always_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Always reported bad behavior lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(View_term, 10))
1. markPassed("Terms and Conditions Link is functional......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_Agree, 10))
1. tap(btn_Agree, 10)
5. markPassed("I Agree button found, User navigate to the Source Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("How did you hear about us? label text found......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())