5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(Source_heart, 10))
1. markPassed("Heart icon found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("How did you hear about us? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Referral, 10))
1. markPassed("Referral label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Do, 10))
1. markPassed("Do you have a referral code? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_code, 10))
1. markPassed("Referral code? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the First Name Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(card_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Card icon found on First Name Screen......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())