5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the First Name and What should we call you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. delay(5)
13. markPassed("PopUp should opened on the screen.......!")
17. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue_popup, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. tap(btn_continue_popup, 10)
9. delay(5)
13. markPassed("User navigate to the Gender Screen.......!")
17. if (waitForElementPresent(mirror_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Mirror icon found on Gender Screen.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("How do you identify? label text found.......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Gender selection successfully.......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_G_Continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Sexual Orientation Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_who, 10))
1. markPassed("Who are you into? label text found.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())