5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Birthday screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(cake_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Cake icon found on Birthday screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("PopUp should opened on the screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue_popup, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue_popup, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Gender Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(mirror_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Mirror icon found on Gender Screen.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("How do you identify? label text found.......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Gender selection successfully.......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_G_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_G_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Sexual Orientation Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(profile_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Profile icon found on next Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())