5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Ethinicity screen......!")
9. delay(10)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(ethnicity_icon, 20))
1. markPassed("Ethnicity icon found on Ethnicty screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Religon Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(book_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Book icon found on Religon screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your religon? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Religon Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_R_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_R_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Ethnicity Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(heart_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Heart icon found on next Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())