1. startExistingApplication("com.spotlove.releaseproduction", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. image = findTestObject("Object Repository/Regression/SC-001 Intro 1/Middle Screen Pic")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(image, 20))
2. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10, STOP_ON_FAILURE))
2. markPassed("Please Create Your SpotLove Account......!")
6. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-07 Welcome To SpotLove"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(Logo_Spotlove, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot.Love Logo Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_txt_first, 10))
1. markPassed("Welcome to Spot.Love lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_txt_Sec, 10))
1. markPassed("Please follow these house rules lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(first_heart_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("First Heart Icon Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Be_kind_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Be Kind lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Treat_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Treat everyone with respect and kindness lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Second_heart_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Second Heart Icon Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Be_your_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Be yourself lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Be_honest_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Be honest about your age, photos, and bio lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Third_heart_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Third Heart Icon Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Be_out_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Be outspoken lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Always_lbl, 10))
1. markPassed("Always reported bad behavior lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(View_term, 10))
1. markPassed("Terms and Conditions Link is functional......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_Agree, 10))
1. tap(btn_Agree, 10)
5. markPassed("I Agree button found, User navigate to the Source Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Source_heart, 10))
1. markPassed("Heart icon found......!")
10. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-08 Source Screen"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(Source_heart, 10))
1. markPassed("Heart icon found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("How did you hear about us? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Referral, 10))
1. markPassed("Referral label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Do, 10))
1. markPassed("Do you have a referral code? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_code, 10))
1. markPassed("Referral code? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the First Name Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(card_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Card icon found on First Name Screen......!")
14. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-09 First Name"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Source screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_Continue2, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. markPassed("User navigate Move forword to the First Name screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Contact_icon, 30))
1. markPassed("Contact icon found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_what, 10))
1. markPassed("What should we call you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_tell, 10))
1. markPassed("Tell us your first name label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(First_Name, 10))
1. setText(First_Name, S_First_Name, 0)
5. markPassed("First name Entered text......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. delay(15)
9. markPassed("User navigate Move forword to the Birth date screen......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(cake_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Cake icon found......!")
18. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-10 Birth date"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the First Name screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Contact_icon, 10))
1. tap(btn_previous_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate Move forword to the Date of Birth screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Cake_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Cake icon found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_what, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your date of birth? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_AGe, 10))
1. markPassed("Age xx label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_This, 10))
1. markPassed("This can't be changed later label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("PopUp should opened on the screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Please, 10))
1. markPassed("Please confirm your birthdate on the PopUp label text found.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_can, 10))
1. markPassed("This can't be changed later label text found.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Age_cofirm, 10))
1. markPassed("Age Confirmation label text found.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(DOB_cofirmation, 10))
1. markPassed("DOB Confirmation label text found.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_edit, 10))
1. tap(btn_edit, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Date of Birth.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("PopUp should opened on the screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue_popup, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue_popup, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Gender Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(mirror_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Mirror icon found on Gender Screen.......!")
22. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-11 Gender Screen"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Birthday screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(cake_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Cake icon found on Birthday screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("PopUp should opened on the screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue_popup, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue_popup, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Gender Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(mirror_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Mirror icon found on Gender Screen.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("How do you identify? label text found.......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Gender selection successfully.......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_G_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_G_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Sexual Orientation Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(profile_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Profile icon found on next Screen.......!")
26. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-12 Sexual Orientation"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Gender screen......!")
9. delay(10)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(mirror_icon, 20))
1. markPassed("Mirror icon found on Gender screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Gender Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(profile_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Profile icon found on Into screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Who, 10))
1. markPassed("Who are you into? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Partner gender Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_S_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_S_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Height Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Scale_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Scale icon found on next Screen.......!")
30. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-13 Height Screen"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Sexual Orientation screen......!")
9. delay(10)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(profile_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Profile icon found on Gender screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Height Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(scale_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Scale icon found on Into screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_How, 10))
1. markPassed("How tall are you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_H_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_H_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Ethnicity Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(ethnicity_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Ethnicity icon found on next Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())