5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. waitForElementPresent(lbl_Find, 10)
9. markPassed("Find the person that checks all your boxes. label text Found on previous Screen......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(F_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate to next screen and 'Make a Match with your solemate' Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(S_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Your Soulmate Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(T_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("It's a match Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Centr_image, 10))
1. markPassed("Center Image Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. waitForElementPresent(lbl_Connect, 10)
9. markPassed("User navigate to next screen and 'Connect with your matches through live video mixers label text found'......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())