5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Relationship Status screen......!")
9. delay(10)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(heart_icon, 20))
1. markPassed("Heart icon found on  Relationship Status screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Family Plan Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(face_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Face icon found on Family Plan screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_tell, 10))
1. markPassed("Tell us about your family label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_do, 10))
1. markPassed("Do you have children? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.comma_sprt_value(random)
9. markPassed("Children Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_what, 10))
1. markPassed("What are your family Plans? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(randoom)
9. markPassed("Family Plan Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_F_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_F_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Education Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(studyHat_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Study Hat icon found on next Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())