5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the Source screen and How did you about us? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_Referral_Continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. markPassed("User navigate Move forword to the First Name screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Contact_icon, 30))
1. markPassed("Contact icon found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_what, 10))
1. markPassed("What should we call you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_tell, 10))
1. markPassed("Tell us your first name label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(First_Name, 10))
1. setText(First_Name, S_First_Name, 0)
5. markPassed("First name Entered text......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. delay(15)
9. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_whats, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate Move forword to the Birth date screen and What's your date of birth? label text found......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())