5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the Gender and How do you identify? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. delay(5)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(profile_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the Gender and Profile icon found on Into screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Who, 10))
1. markPassed("Who are you into? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Partner gender Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. delay(5)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_tall, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate to the Height Screen and How tall are you? label text found on next Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())