5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. waitForElementPresent(logo, 10)
5. markPassed("Back button Found......!")
9. markPassed("Spot Love Logo Found......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(F_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Make a Match Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(S_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Your Soulmate Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(T_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("It's a match Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Centr_image, 10))
1. markPassed("Center Image Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User Navigate to the Third Screen......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())