5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Vices screen......!")
9. delay(10)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(bottle_icon, 20))
1. markPassed("bottle icon found on Vices screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Politics Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Justics_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Justics icon found on Politics screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What are your political views? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Political view Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_P_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_P_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Gallery Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Gallery_icon, 10))
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())