1. startExistingApplication("com.spotlove.releaseproduction", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Education screen......!")
9. delay(10)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(hat_icon, 20))
1. markPassed("Hat icon found on Education screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Vices Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(bottle_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Bottle icon found on Vices screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What are your vices? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_toggle_M, 10))
1. tap(btn_toggle_M, 10)
5. markPassed("Marijuana Toggle button On......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_toggle_S, 10))
1. tap(btn_toggle_S, 10)
5. markPassed("Smoking Toggle button On......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_toggle_A, 10))
1. tap(btn_toggle_A, 10)
5. markPassed("Alcohol Toggle button On......!")
9. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(A_random)
13. markPassed("Alcohol Toggle button On......!")
17. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(S_random)
21. markPassed("Smoking Selected......!")
25. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(M_random)
29. markPassed("Marijuana Selected......!")
33. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_V_Continue, 10))
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())