5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_whats, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the Religion screen and What's your Religion? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. delay(5)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your Reletionship Status? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(heart_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Heart icon found on Reletionship Status screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your Reletionship Status? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Reletionship Status Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Children & Family Plan Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_tell, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your Reletionship Status? label text found......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())