5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the First Name and What should we call you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Cake_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate Move forword to the Birthdate screen nad Cake icon found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_what, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your date of birth? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_AGe, 10))
1. markPassed("Age xx label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_This, 10))
1. markPassed("This can't be changed later label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
2. markFailed("Continue button is not working.....!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())