5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Height screen......!")
9. delay(10)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(scale_icon, 20))
1. markPassed("Scale icon found on Height screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Ethnicity Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(ethnicity_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Ethnicity icon found on Ethnicity screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your ethnicity? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Ethnicity Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_E_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_E_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Height Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(book_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Holly Book icon found on next Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())