5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_whats, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the Ethnicity screen and What's your Ethnicity? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. delay(5)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your religon? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(book_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Book icon found on Religon screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your religon? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Religon Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Ethnicity Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_relation, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your Relationship? label text found......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())