5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. startExistingApplication("com.spotlove.releaseproduction", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the First Name and What should we call you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Cake_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate Move forword to the Birthdate screen nad Cake icon found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_what, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your date of birth? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_AGe, 10))
1. markPassed("Age xx label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_This, 10))
1. markPassed("This can't be changed later label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. markPassed("PopUp should opened on the screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Please, 10))
1. markPassed("Please confirm your birthdate on the PopUp label text found.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_can, 10))
1. markPassed("This can't be changed later label text found.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Age_cofirm, 10))
1. markPassed("Age Confirmation label text found.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(DOB_cofirmation, 10))
1. markPassed("DOB Confirmation label text found.......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_edit, 10))
1. tap(btn_edit, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Date of Birth.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. delay(5)
13. markPassed("PopUp should opened on the screen.......!")
17. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue_popup, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. tap(btn_continue_popup, 10)
9. delay(5)
13. markPassed("User navigate to the Gender Screen.......!")
17. if (waitForElementPresent(mirror_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Mirror icon found on Gender Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())