5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. waitForElementPresent(lbl_Make, 10)
9. markPassed("Make a match with Your Soulmate label text Found on previous Screen......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(F_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate to next screen and 'Spot The Perfect' Lbl text Found .........!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(S_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Someone Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(T_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Find The Person Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Centr_image, 10))
1. markPassed("Center Image Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
2. markFailed("Somethong missing Please check......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())