1. startExistingApplication("com.spotlove.releaseproduction", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. image = findTestObject("Object Repository/Regression/SC-001 Intro 1/Middle Screen Pic")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(image, 20))
1. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-01 First Intro Screen"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(logo, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot Love Logo Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(F_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot The Perfect Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(S_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Someone Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(T_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Find The Person Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Centr_image, 10))
1. markPassed("Center Image Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User Navigate to the Second Screen......!")
5. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-02 Second Intro Screen"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. waitForElementPresent(logo, 10)
5. markPassed("Back button Found......!")
9. markPassed("Spot Love Logo Found......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(F_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Make a Match Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(S_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Your Soulmate Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(T_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("It's a match Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Centr_image, 10))
1. markPassed("Center Image Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User Navigate to the Third Screen......!")
9. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-03 Third Intro Screen"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. waitForElementPresent(logo, 10)
5. markPassed("Back button Found......!")
9. markPassed("Spot Love Logo Found......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(F_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot The Perfect Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(S_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Someone Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(T_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Find The Person Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Centr_image, 10))
1. markPassed("Center Image Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User Navigate to the Sign-In selection Screen......!")
13. markPassed("Intro Screens Passed Successfully")
17. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10, STOP_ON_FAILURE))
1. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-04 Sign In Selection"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(F_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot Love At First Sight label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(S_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Select an account to Continue label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_Continue_WPN, 10))
1. tap(btn_Continue_WPN, 10)
5. markPassed("User Navigate to Phone Numebr Screen......!")
5. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-05 Phone Number Enter Screen"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(spotlove_logo, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot.Love Logo Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. markPassed("Back Button Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_first_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Sign in to Spot.Love label text is found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Second_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Continue with your phone number label text is found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(flag_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Country Flag Icon is found......!")
5. tap(flag_icon, 10)
9. markPassed("Country slection dropdown is opened......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(search_box, 10))
1. setText(search_box, C_Name, 10)
5. markPassed("Country Name Entered in the Search Box......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(First_index, 10))
1. tap(First_index, 10)
5. markPassed("Country Selection Successfully......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Enter_Phonenumber, 10))
1. setText(Enter_Phonenumber, PhoneNumber, 10)
5. markPassed("Phon number Entered......!")
9. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-06 OTP Screen"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(spotlove_logo, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot.Love Logo Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. markPassed("Back Button Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_first_text, 60))
1. markPassed("Enter your verification code label text is found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Second_text, 10))
1. markPassed("We're sent a pin to +16505559876 label text is found......!")
5. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Smoke/OTP/android.widget.EditText - -"), 15)
9. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Smoke/OTP/android.widget.EditText - - (1)"), "1", 2)
13. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Smoke/OTP/android.widget.EditText - - (2)"), "2", 2)
17. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Smoke/OTP/android.widget.EditText - - (3)"), "3", 2)
21. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Smoke/OTP/android.widget.EditText - - (4)"), "4", 2)
25. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Smoke/OTP/android.widget.EditText - - (5)"), "5", 2)
29. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Smoke/OTP/android.widget.EditText - - (6)"), "6", 2)
33. com.spotlove.Utility.Verify()
13. markPassed("User Authenticated......!")
17. callTestCase(findTestCase("Test Cases/Regression/LookUps/SL-07 Welcome To SpotLove"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (waitForElementPresent(Logo_Spotlove, 10))
2. markFailed("Spot.Love Logo not Found......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())