5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_who, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the Into screen and How tall are you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. delay(5)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("How tall are you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(scale_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Scale icon found on Into screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Ethnicity Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_what, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your Ethnicity label text found on next Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())