5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_back()
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_how, 10))
1. markPassed("User navigate back to the Into screen and How tall are you? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. delay(5)
5. com.spotlove.Utility.tap_Continue()
9. delay(5)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your ethnicity? label text found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(ethnicity_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Ethnicity icon found on Ethnicity screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_What, 10))
1. markPassed("What's your ethnicity? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Ethnicity Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_E_Continue, 10))
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())