1. startExistingApplication("com.spotlove.releaseproduction", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. if (waitForElementPresent(logo, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot Love Logo Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(F_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Spot The Perfect Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(S_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Someone Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(T_lbl_text, 10))
1. markPassed("Find The Person Lbl text Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(Centr_image, 10))
1. markPassed("Center Image Found......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User Navigate to the Second Screen......!")
9. takeScreenshot("test screenshot")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())