5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_back, 10))
1. tap(btn_back, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate back to the Gender screen......!")
9. delay(10)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(mirror_icon, 20))
1. markPassed("Mirror icon found on Gender screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Gender Screen......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(profile_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Profile icon found on Into screen......!")
5. if (waitForElementPresent(lbl_Who, 10))
1. markPassed("Who are you into? label text found......!")
5. com.spotlove.Utility.dating_Pref(random)
9. markPassed("Partner gender Selection successfully......!")
13. if (waitForElementPresent(btn_S_Continue, 10))
1. tap(btn_S_Continue, 10)
5. markPassed("User navigate to the Height Screen.......!")
9. if (waitForElementPresent(Scale_icon, 10))
1. markPassed("Scale icon found on next Screen.......!")
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())